[{"id": 2588, "question": "Elizabeth Mitchell's new \"Liberty's Torch\" is the fascinating story of how the Statue of Liberty came to be. The Statue of Liberty's rough history is explored in \"Liberty's Torch\". Frederic Auguste Bartholdi is an all-but-forgotten figure in American history. He was, however, responsible for one of the most enduring symbols of the United States: the Statue of Liberty. A Frenchman from Alsace, he designed and built the Statue of Liberty which stood on Bedloe's Island in New York Harbor. How this statue came to be is the fascinating subject of Elizabeth Michell's new book \"Liberty's Torch\". The power of Mitchell's narrative is convincing . We recognize the Statue of Liberty now as a symbol of hope and opportunity for a nation of immigrants. At the time, though, people could not see that-nor ...\n\nQ: What was the main reason for Bartholdi to build the Statue of Liberty?", "options": ["To finish his education in the arts.", "To mark his friendship with Ferdinand.", "To create something better than Egyptian monuments.", "To achieve his dream to create the largest statue."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1391, "question": "In the market of luxury brands, Chinese consumers are only second to the Japanese in the world. Across the globe it's clear that the young generation are increasingly relying on expensive brands for their self-image. Personally I am a fashion-lover, at least in spirit. I love to look at clothes and shoes. But I don't understand why people spend large amounts of money on designer labels. Certainly, young people, whether in China or elsewhere, should be building their self-confidence in other ways. When a young woman shows off a handbag worth two months' salary, that's a scary thing. What are the psychological factors forcing young people to take on debt for designer items? The desire to say, \"Hey, look at me. I'm wealthy. I have social status.\" Scientists have found the acquisition of luxur...\n\nQ: The author finds it hard to understand   _  .", "options": ["why people like to look at clothes and shoes", "why Chinese consume so many luxury brands", "why young people build their self-image through clothes", "why people spend so much money on designer labels"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3311, "question": "It is amazing to note that the Internet is still such a new device, and yet it is one of the fastest and most powerful media tools. But think about it for a moment. On the Internet, a big online company can be run by two guys out of their garage. So it is only reasonable that people shopping on the Net would be a little _ of the security levels. Internet giants such as Microsoft knew consumer confidence was the key to getting virtual shopping off the ground, and they work hard to make people feel safe to shop online. Credit card companies, too, quickly saw the potential for Internet shopping, and have installed things like online shopping insurance for people. If you ever have a problem with your online credit purchases, many credit card companies will happily refund your money and then se...\n\nQ: The following are thought to have made contributions to the popularity of online shoppingEXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["internet companies", "courier companies", "advertising companies", "credit card companies"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1936, "question": "My sister Grace Halloran spent most of her teen years in and out of the juvenile institutions for minor offenses but, at 18 she was sent to prison for stealing a car. After three years behind the bars, she was released. Only a few years later, she was given a sentence far worse--she had an incurable and progressive disorder and would be totally blind. Meanwhile, Grace was also happily pregnant but terrified she would never see her child's face. She believed she would succeed as a mother, although \"success\" had never been in her vocabulary before. She managed well despite fading vision. For years she kept consulting specialists about her eye problems, only to be told that her son would also be blind by the time he was a teenager. She swore to find something, anything, to prevent him from fa...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that Grace used to be   _  .", "options": ["aggressive", "troublesome", "ignorant", "competitive"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2706, "question": "Country singer and songwriter Adrienne Young brings together music and agricultural activities.She even included seeds in the album cover of her first CD. Adrienne Young wants people to know that she supports the movement in America to increase local farming.She offers information about agricultural issues on her Web site.And now part of the moneyfrom her third and newest release, \"Room to Grow\",will be donated to help support community gardens. Adrienne Young's family has lived in Florida for seven generations.Her ancestors helped develop the agriculture industry there.The state of Florida is the nation's second largest producer of fruits and vegetables, 'after California. Adrienne Young has said that her interest in nature was shaped by the fact that she did not grow up on a farm.She gre...\n\nQ: It can be learned from the passage that   _   .", "options": ["Adrienne Young's parents used to be farmers", "Adrienne Young grew up on a farm", "Florida is good for farming", "no old houses existing on the farm belongs to Adrienne Young"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2155, "question": "The Haitian tsunami gave scientists a chance to find out how well vital and potentially life-saving warning systems were working. Noaa's Pacific Marine Environmental Laboratory has developed a warning system that picks up signals of tsunamis directly from the sea-floor. It is called Dart-the Deep-ocean Assessment and Reporting of Tsunamis. If seismometers detect an earthquake, the Dart buoys will determine what is happening to sea levels, and whether a big wave might be on the way. This information is then sent via satellite to a central location which can organize an alarm. Within 50 minutes of the Haiti earthquake, this system was able to issue an alarm to other countries in the Caribbean to say that a small tsunami had been caused to start, and that was unlikely to affect them. Dr Berna...\n\nQ: How many buoys would at least be needed for global tsunami warnings within half an hour?", "options": ["150", "100", "75", "50"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1467, "question": "New rules and behavior standards for the middle school students came out in March. Middle school is going to use a new way to decide who the top students are. The best students won't only have high marks. They will also be kids who don't dye their hair, smoke or drink. The following are some of the new rules. Tell the truth. Have you ever copied others' work in an exam? Don't do it again if you did it before! That's not something an honest student should do. If you have played computer games for two hours in your room, don't tell your parents you have done your homework. Do more at school. Good students love animals and care for other people. April is a bird-loving month in China. Did your school do anything to celebrate? If so, you should join it! In this way, you can learn more about ani...\n\nQ: The school new rules will help kids by telling them   _  .", "options": ["how they can study well", "what they should do at home", "what is right and what is wrong", "how they can help themselves"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2168, "question": "The International Space Station,one of the most ambitious space projects ever and a key launching board for exploration of the solar system,turns l0 years old Thursday. On Nov.20,1998,the first part of the space station was launched by the Russians from Kazakhstan.NASA followed up two weeks later with Piece No 2 carried up by a space shuttle. The space station has grown into a giant outpost 355 km up,home to three people at any given time--soon to be six. Thanks to the newly arrived shuttle Endeavour,the space station now has five sleep stations,two baths,two kitchens and two mini--gyms.Ahogether,there are nine rooms,three of which are full scale labs. The United States has financed the main part of the project,estimated to cost some 100 billion dollars.Fifteen other countries have also co...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true about Endeav our according to the passage?", "options": ["Endeavour is a newly built shuttle", "Endeavour is part of the space station", "Endeavour didn't get close to the space station", "Endeavour carried a lot of equipment for the apace station"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2351, "question": "Centerville High School Essay Contest \"Write All About It\" Calling All Aspiring Authors--Centerville High School Essay Contest *Rules 1.Students are asked to present essays of 500 to 700 words of their own work. Any essay containing material plagiarized from another source will be disqualified . 2.Manuscripts should be typed double-spaced,with the student's name,address,and grade level on a separate sheet of paper. 3.Essays must be turned in by 4:00 p.m. on November 30.They can be brought to Mrs. Elton in Rom 104 or to Mr. Markham in the school library. *Essay-Writing Tips 1.Catch your readers' interests--Your opening should immediately pull your readers into your essay. Asking a question or starting with an story,quotation,or surprising statement is a good way to do this. 2.Create a pictu...\n\nQ: The prize section of the poster is included in order to  _  .", "options": ["show organizations how to donate prizes", "inform teachers of the prizes available", "persuade students to enter the essay contest", "convince students to buy the local newspaper"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2075, "question": "High Speed Book Scanner Simply turning pages of a book quickly may not seem like the best way to scan it. A Japanese research group at Tokyo University has created new software that allows hundreds of pages to be scanned within minutes. Scanning text is normally a boring process with each page having to be inserted into a scanner, but the team led by Professor Masatoshi Ishikawa uses a high speed camera that takes 500 pictures a second to scan pages as they are turned by workers. Normal scanners can only scan the information that is actually before them on the page. This high speed book scanner uses a camera that captures pages at 1000fps as they are turned. A system built in allows it to automatically correct any changes to the text due to the page bending as well as light differences due...\n\nQ: What is Ishikawa's attitude towards the development of the scanning system?", "options": ["Optimistic.", "Uncertain.", "Disapproving.", "Cautious."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 119, "question": "Winter is the time of year when people feel very blessed. This isn't because people feel thankful for the cold weather, nor because the important festivals---Christmas or Spring Festival---offer an excuse to celebrate. In fact, \"Bless you!\" is a common response if someone sneezes, a symptom of catching a cold or the flu. Colds and the flu are the most common illnesses of autumn and winter as the weather gets colder. Viruses cause them. If you get one you will feel annoyed, but it is not usually serious. The flu is spread from person to person when we come into contact with a person with the virus. We get the virus on our hands and then we touch our noses and our mouths. We can pass on the flu before we realize we have it. You can infect others one day before symptoms develop and for up to ...\n\nQ: The passage is intended to tell us   _  .", "options": ["how to keep healthy .", "the causes of flu .", "the influence of flu .", "what to do about flu."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2937, "question": "Crazy is our new normal. With two teenage boys and three little boys, our family is restless--to the baseball field, track field and piano lessons. Even though we've limited each boy's activities and try our best to defend our family time, it seems that we're in a constant state of flight. \"Embrace it. Roll with it,\" my husband, Lonny, says, \"It's going to be like this for a while.\" He is right. It's likely that life will continue to go forward before it slows down. But I remembered the still, quiet days that our family used to enjoy. I missed long walks through the park when we held the boys' little hands. I longed for lazy Saturday afternoons under the tree in our backyard. I wanted to slip back a few years, when busyness was the exception and not the rule. One night, after a particularl...\n\nQ: How did the author feel about life before the night sitting on the porch with the family?", "options": ["Confused.", "Satisfied.", "Bored.", "Terrified."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 887, "question": "If you're one of the 13 million Americans still struggling to find a job, or wanting to change jobs, a lot of your applications are probably being swallowed up by the \"the black hole.\" That's when you send in a job application and never receive any follow-up from the company.In fact, only 25 out of 100 applications ever get looked at by companies. Now, a remarkable new service is helping job seekers instantly track almost every application they submit so they actually know what's going on.It's called Start Wire. corn and it lets job seekers track their applications and find out whether or not their applications have been reviewed, dismissed, or are still being considered. How does it work? When you fill out a job application via a company website, you'll typically get an auto confirmation ...\n\nQ: You can probably read the passage from   _", "options": ["a newspaper", "a website", "a poster", "a magazine"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1573, "question": "Immigration is the act of coming to a foreign country to live. The act of leaving one's country to settle in another is called emigration. Immigrants who flee their country because of persecution, war, or such disasters as famines or epidemics are known as refugees or displaced persons. Most people find it very hard to pull up roots in their native land and move to a strange country. But throughout history, countless millions of people have done so. The heaviest immigration worldwide took place from the early 1800's to the Great Depression, the economic hard times of the 1930's. In that period, about 60 million people moved to a new land. Most came from Europe. More than half immigrated to the United States. Other destinations included Canada, Argentina, Brazil, Australia, New Zealand, and...\n\nQ: The main reason for immigration is   _  according to the passage.", "options": ["slavery trade", "religious persecution", "economic opportunity", "political unrest"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1593, "question": "The college entrance exam is not only a big challenge for Chinese high school students, but also a very important exam in the lives of South Korean students. Although the long, cold winter has already started in South Korea, the annual national exams have made the atmosphere very heated. More than 675,000 South Korean high school graduates took the college entrance exam last Wednesday. They usually take exams in Korean, maths, sociology , history and foreign languages. Officially there is one college place for every 1.33 students. But because all the students want to go to the top universities in the country, the competition can reach one place for 10 students. The students want to attend these colleges for both their famous names and better job opportunities. Because students face fierce ...\n\nQ: Before students are allowed to colleges   _  .", "options": ["they will be interviewed", "they will ask questions of colleges", "they will not be tested any more", "first they will pay all the education fee at all"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 58, "question": "A desert is a beautiful land of silence and space. The sun shines, the wind blows, and time and space seem endless. Nothing is soft. The sand and rocks are hard, and many of the plants even have hard needles instead of leaves. The size and location of the world's deserts are always changing. Over millions of years, as climates change and mountains rise, new dry and wet areas develop. But within the last 100 yeas, deserts have been growing at a frightening speed. This is partly because of natural changes, but the greatest makers are humans. Humans can make deserts, but humans can also prevent their growth. Algeria Mauritania is planting a similar wall around Nouakchott, the capital. Iran puts a thin covering of petroleum on sandy areas and plants trees. The oil keeps the water and small tre...\n\nQ: We can guess that Mauritania and Algeria belong to   _  .", "options": ["Asian countries", "American countries", "European counties", "African countries"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2175, "question": "Summer school is something a kid will never forget.For some, it's a way to advance past their classmates.For most, summer school is' a requirement in order to graduate with their classmates I can remember being forced into taking a summer school course.It was not the school that forced me into this awkward situation it was my mother. I was a 16-year-old kid in a new school; My school did not offer summer courses so I had to take my course at an alternative school in the city.It was an experience I will never forget.I was not concerned with making friends.I was there to get credit for a course that I should have received credit for the previous semester.It was.my doing that landed me in the situation and it was important that I understood this. The fees were lowest but the experience was am...\n\nQ: What does the author think of summer school?", "options": ["He thinks it is awkward.", "He thinks it is significant.", "He doesn't think it is suitable.", "He thinks nothing of it."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3, "question": "There is probably no field of human activity in which our values and lifestyles are shown more clearly and strongly than they are in the clothes that we choose to wear.The dress of an individual is a kind of \"sign language\" that communicates a set of information and is usually the basis on which immediate impressions are formed.Traditionally,a concern for clothes was considered to be an affair of females,while men took pride in the fact that they were completely lacking in clothes consciousness . This type of American culture is by degrees changing as man dress takes on greater variety and color.Even as early as 1955,a researcher in Michigan said that _ White collar workers in particular viewed dress as a symbol of ability,which could be used to impress or influence others,especially in th...\n\nQ: The passage tells us that   _  .", "options": ["our values and lifestyles are in no field of human activity", "the clothes that we choose to wear have something to do with our values and lifestyles", "our values and lifestyles are from the sign language", "the clothes we choose to wear depend on a set of information and immediate impression"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2185, "question": "Linda and Lucy were best friends. They graduated from high school and went to the same college for further studies. After some days Linda found that her friend was behaving strangely. She would remain quiet, sleep too much and turn wild, very often. At first, Linda thought it was just because of the problems she had met in her studies. However, Lucy became even stranger over time. Finally, Linda couldn't take it any longer and asked Lucy about her strange behavior. Lucy broke into tears and said that she was going around with a boy, who was taking drugs and forcing her to take them, too. Linda was shocked by her story. She then advised her friend to leave the boy. She reminded Lucy of her dreams of becoming a successful doctor and encouraged her to set an example for others. She also remin...\n\nQ: What problem did Lucy meet?", "options": ["She lost her best friend", "She was ill at that time", "She dated a troublesome boy", "She fell behind others in study"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3165, "question": "What is your favorite English letter? Many of you may say Q. Why? Because so many of you chat with your friends on QQ. What do you like about QQ? What do you talk about? The CCTV reporter, Miss Wang, interviews three kids. Let's listen to what they say. When do you chat on QQ? What do you talk about? Lin yuhan, Xi'an: On weekends. We talk about homework and chat with each other. Tang Xuting, Shanghai: At weekends and when I don't have much homework. We exchange test answers and chat. Yang yuhang, Dalian: Our class goes online together at 4:00----6:00pm on weekends. We complain about homework, chat and talk about computer games. What do you put on your QQ blog ? Lin: I put good articles I have found online on my blog. I also write articles myself. They are about funny things that have happe...\n\nQ: Which one is TURE according to this article?", "options": ["Lin says QQ is very helpful to their friendships.", "Yang says he can chat freely with many friends and relax on QQ.", "Tang says QQ is a good space for them to make a record of their lives.", "Tang says he chats on QQ on weekends though he has lots of homework."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1158, "question": "What does the future hold for the problem of housing? A good deal depends, of course, on the meaning of \"future\". If one is thinking in terms of science fiction and the space age, it is at least possible to assume that man will have solved such trivial and earthly problems as housing. Writers of science fiction, from H.G. Wells onwards, have had little to say on the subject. They have conveyed the suggestion that men will live in great comfort, with every imaginable apparatus to make life smooth, healthy and easy, if not happy. But they have not said what his house will be made of. Perhaps some new building material, as yet unimagined, will have been discovered or invented at least. One may be certain that bricks and mortar(,) will long have gone out of fashion. But the problems of the nex...\n\nQ: When the writer says that the worst situations will occur in the hottest parts of the world or in backward areas, he is referring to the fact that in these parts   _  .", "options": ["the population growth will be the greatest.", "standards of building are low.", "only minimum shelter will be possible.", "there is not enough ground space."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2231, "question": "Why texting harms your IQ The regular use of text messages and e-mails can lower the IQ more than twice as much as smoking marijuana . That is the statement of researchers who have found that tapping away on a mobile phone or computer keypad or checking for electronic messages temporarily knocks up to 10 points off the user's IQ. This rate of decline in intelligence compares unfavorably with the four-point drop in IQ associated with smoking marijuana, according to British researchers, who have described the phenomenon of improved stupidity as \"infomania\". The research conducted by Hewlett Packard, the technology company, has concluded that it is mainly a problem for adult workers, especially men. It is concluded that too much use of modern technology can damage a person's mind. It can caus...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that \"infomania\"   _  .", "options": ["has a positive influence on one's IQ", "results in the change of part of the brain", "lies in the problem of lack of concentration", "is caused by too much use of modern technology"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2210, "question": "Christmas Day, the birthday of Jesus Christ, is the most important festival in prefix = st1 /Britainand some other countries. On Christmas Eve, people usually tell their children to put their stockings at the end of their beds before they go to sleep. Children believe Santa Claus, with the other name of Father Christmas, will come during the night and fill their stockings with Christmas presents. Actually , Father Christmas is children's father. He dresses up in a red coat and waits until children fall asleep. Then he goes into children's bedrooms, and puts small presents in their stockings. When children are no longer young, they know who Father Christmas really is. Not only children but also their parents enjoy Christmas stockings. They also have stockings. Early on the morning of Christ...\n\nQ: \"Santa Claus\"is another way of saying  _  .", "options": ["Christmas Day", "Christmas presents", "Christmas Eve", "Father Christmas"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 694, "question": "Jenny went to visit her friends in New York last weekend.Her friends met her at the airport on Friday afternoon and drove her to the hotel.They had dinner at a Chinese restaurant and went to see a film after that. Jenny and her friends set out early on Saturday morning for a farm and stayed there until Sunday morning.During their stay, they went fishing and swimming in the small river on the farm.They played football in the field and enjoyed a big meal around a camp fire , singing and dancing till late into the night. Nobody could get up early on Sunday morning.So when they got back to New York City, it was about three o'clock in the afternoon.They drove right to the airport because Jenny didn't want to miss her plane back home.Jenny only stayed in New York for two nights but she had a gre...\n\nQ: How did Jenny get to New York?", "options": ["By train.", "By bus.", "By plane.", "On foot."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2465, "question": "For a long time now, I've been fascinated by common phrases and their origins- and just why we say what we say. I decided to consult the experts, sort through all the research and compile the answers. Here are a few of the standouts. Q: Why do we\"tie the knot \"when we get married? A: Knots have been a common metaphor in marriage ceremonies all over the world and through time. The expression means\"to unite in manage\". In the Hindu marriage ceremony, the groom ties a ribbon around the bride's neck. In ancient Rome, the bride wore a belt that was tied in a knot. The groom would then unfasten it on their first night together as husband and wife. Q: Why do we say\"Many happy returns\"? A: The phrase is short for\"Many happy returns of the day\", which is to say,\"May this day return many times\"or\"Ma...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["\"Tie the knot\"has different meanings in different cultures.", "\"Many happy returns\"is often used when people celebrate birthdays.", "\"It's not over till the fat lady sings\"got its start in 1976.", "\"Under the weather\"means the weather is bad."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2777, "question": "How To Apply for USA Passports Online If you live in the United States, and you're planning a trip abroad, it is important to apply for new passports at least 2 months in advance (to avoid extra charges for an expedited passport processing). You can now get the application for a passport online. Some directions are detailed below: Downloading the passport application: The USA passport application, Form DS-11, is available for download on the US Department of State's website. *The passport application form is a Portable Document Format (PDF) file, and your computer must have Adobe Acrobat Reader to open it. If you do not have Adobe Acrobat Reader, you must first download the Adobe Acrobat software. You can do so by clicking here. *If you would like to download a blank application, click her...\n\nQ: Where can the passage be found probably?", "options": ["A newspaper", "A magazine", "A website", "A travelling brochure"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3010, "question": "To me, life without music would not be exciting. I realize that this is not true for everybody. Many people get along quite well without going to the concert, and listening to the record. But music plays an important part in everyone's life, whether he realizes it or not. Try to imagine, for example, what films or TV plays would be like without music. Would the feelings, the moving plot, and the greatest interests, be so exciting or dramatic? I'm not sure about it. Now, we have been speaking of music in its more common meaning----the kind of music we hear in the concert hall. But if we look at some parts of music more closely, we discover them in our everyday life too----in the rhythm of the sea, the _ of a bird in the woods and so on. So music surely has meaning for everyone, in some way ...\n\nQ: From the text, we learn that many people  _  .", "options": ["don't realize the importance of music", "get along quite well without music", "go to the concert instead of enjoying music", "think music would be less exciting than films"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1456, "question": "Read the advertisements carefully.Then answer the questions that follow. INTERESTED IN CHILDCARE? Qualified person or preschool teacher needed for busy childcare center, south of the river.Full-time work guaranteed.Immediate start necessary.The candidate must be able to work as a co-operative team member.Phone 6345 2345 for an interview and fax resume to 6345 2345. WE NEED OFFICE CLEANERS! Three people are required for professional cleaning in the CBD area.Working hours from 5:00 pm on Mondays, Wednesdays & Fridays.Approximately five hours per shift.A good record is necessary.Experience preferred.Phone 6345 7843 now. WANT TO WORK AS A DENTAL NURSE? This is an exciting opportunity for a qualified dental nurse with a confident and cheerful personality to work in the School Dental Health Sche...\n\nQ: The office cleaners will be required to work about   _   hours a week.", "options": ["15", "5", "10", "20"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3088, "question": "Science isn't something mysterious, only for the few. Every one of us--whether a poet, worker, or physicist has to be able to think scientifically, and to understand some science, such as whether to smoke, what to eat, and what protection to use. Even for decisions that don't depend on some scientific facts, science remains the proven set of best methods for getting exact information about the world. Some people will end up as policy-makers in government or business. People such as these make decisions that affect the life of everyone, and most of them know no more about science than does the rest of the general public. Yet they are called upon to decide what to do about nuclear reactors , global warming, environmental toxins , expensive space programs, and biomedical research. It's nonsci...\n\nQ: According to the passage, who can decide whether the milk we drink can safely come from cows treated with medicine?", "options": ["Scientists", "Young people", "The public", "Policy-makers"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3158, "question": "TheCastle of Monteriggioni Located in central Tuscany,the Castle of Monteriggioniwas built by the Republic of Siena at the beginning of the 13th century in orderto defend its southern border against Florence.With their impressive towers, they feature in Dante's Divine Comedy. MainSights Inside the town are the Church of Santa Maria Assunta,the battlements on the town walls and the small \"Monteriggioni in Arme\" museum, where there are models andlife-size armors . Every July within the wall of the town a special eventis celebrated: the Medieval Festival of Monteriggioni, one of the mostbeautiful festivals in the region. The city goes back in time to the MiddleAges, the streets are filled up with people in period costume creating a realatmosphere. Dances, live performances, music, theatre, ki...\n\nQ: Which of the following you cannot seein the Castle of Monteriggioni ?", "options": ["Tower", "Vineyards", "Church", "Performance"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3378, "question": "New rules for pubs and clubs, including a ban on drinking games like the awful \"dentist's chair\", will be introduced in Britain this year to prevent the heavy drinking culture, which costs the country billions of pounds a year. Other activities like \"all you can drink for 10 pounds \", \"women drink free\" nights and speed drinking competitions will also be banned. But, on the other hand, offers of cheap alcohol in supermarkets will not be affected, which is widely regarded as one of the main sources of Britain's problems with under-age and over-drinking. Doctors and health experts argue that the government has failed to use its most effective weapon, the taxation of minimum price controls on alcohol. Home Secretary Alan Johnson said that the government and the industry had a duty to act on h...\n\nQ: What is probably the most effective way to control alcohol?", "options": ["bans", "education", "force", "taxation"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1460, "question": "When, after a year of being alone on his island, Robinson Crusoe sees a footprint in the sand, the reader of Robinson Crusoe trembles. Will Crusoe find another human being to end his loneliness? Is the footprint the sign of an enemy? Since 1719, when Daniel Defoe wrote Robinson Crusoe, thousands of people who enjoy English novels have thrilled to this great adventure story. But few know how the story came to be written. Robinson Crusoe was the first English novel. Its birth brought together the misadventures of a Scotch \"failure\" and the untapped imagination of an aging English scribbler. Near the end of the Seventeenth Century, the hot-tempered Alexander Selkirk was charged with bad conduct while in church. Rather than face this charge, he ran away to sea. Several years later, Selkirk fou...\n\nQ: According to this passage , which of the following statements is not true?", "options": ["Robinson Crusoe was a successful novel.", "Even if Alexander Selkirk had not lived on the island of Juan Femande, Robinson Crusoe would still have been written.", "Daniel Defoe lived partly by hard work and partly by his \" wits \".", "With the writing of Robinson Crusoe , the English novel was born."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1137, "question": "Americans have contributed to many art forms, and jazz, a type of music, is one of the art forms started in the United States. Black Americans, who sang and played the music of their homeland, created jazz. Jazz is a mixture of the music of Africa, the work songs the slaves sang, and religious music. Improvisation is an important part of jazz. This is why a jazz song sounds a little different each time it is played. Jazz bands formed in the late 1800s. They played in bars and clubs in many towns and cities of the South, especially New Orleans. New Orleans is an international seaport, and people from all over the world come to New Orleans to hear jazz. Jazz became more and more popular. By the 1920s, jazz was popular all over the United States. By the 1940s, you could hear jazz not only in ...\n\nQ: What can be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["American Art Forms", "The Development of Jazz", "The Music of Black Americans", "The Birthplace of Jazz"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 319, "question": "Cutting global warming pollution would not only make the planet healthier, it would make people healthier too, new research suggested. Cutting carbon dioxide emissions could save millions of lives, mostly by reducing preventable deaths from heart and lung diseases, according to studies released Wednesday and published in a special issue of The Lancet, a British medical journal. \"Relying on fossil fuels leads to unhealthy lifestyles, increasing our chances of getting sick and in some cases takes years from our lives,\" US Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius said in a telecast briefing from her home state of Kansas. \"As greenhouse gas emissions go down, so do deaths from cardiovascular and respiratory diseases. This is not a small effect.\" Instead of looking at the health il...\n\nQ: According to Kathleen Sebelius,   _  .", "options": ["sometimes it takes years to see the bad effects caused by consuming fossil fuels", "without greenhouse gas emissions, people would not die of cardiovascular and respiratory diseases", "the main reason why people get sick is that they rely on fossil fuels", "deaths from cardiovascular and respiratory diseases are closely related to greenhouse gas emissions"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3047, "question": "Schoolgirls have been wearing such short skirts at Paget High School in Branston that they've been ordered to wear trousers instead. All skirts will be banned from September. Tight-fitting trousers will also be forbidden and Muslim head-dresses will have to be \"school blue'' color. Head teacher Don Smith said, \"One of the big problems for us at the school has been the number of girls who have been wearing inappropriately short skirts. This has been an area of particular concern at a time when there has been a lot of material nationally about the sexualisation of young people.\" He also said, \" It will be impractical to police the length of girls' skirts. A blanket ban will be easier for staff to put into practice. We did not want to arrive at a situation where we were telling girls their sk...\n\nQ: The girls at Paget High School are not allowed to wear skirts in that    _  .", "options": ["short skirts give people the impression of sexualisation", "short skirts are too expensive for parents to afford", "the headmaster doesn't like girls wearing short skirts", "the girls wearing short skirts will be at the risk of being laughed at"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2746, "question": "Many of you may wonder what else to do besides watching TV or surfing the Internet on weekends.Why not have a picnic? Junior 2 students at Beijing No.4 Middle Schoo1 had a \"King of cooking\" competition* Earlier this month,about 300 students at the schoo1 went to a suburb of Beijing to have the contest.They were divided into 24 groups.Each group had buyers,slicers ,firemakers.washers and cooks. Firemakers faced the most problems during the time.Some of them had no idea how to keep fire burning. \"The fire kept going out.we had to blow at the sparks and put on corn leaves and old newspapers,\"said Wu Mofei,13. \"It took us an hour to make the fire.Our eyes had tears from all the smoke and our faces became dirty,\"he added. When the fires were finally made,the cooks became the busiest people.Huan...\n\nQ: Which of the following was not the problem some firemakers met?", "options": ["They didn't know how to keep fire burning.", "They spent a long time in making a fire.", "The fire kept going out.", "They didn't have enough corn leaves and old newspapers."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1378, "question": "Facebook users may feel socially successful in the web world but they are more likely to perform poorly in exams. The majority of students who use Facebook every day are doing badly compared with those who don't. About 83% of British 16 to 24-year-old people are using social networking site such as Facebook and MySpace, to keep in touch with friends and organize their social activities. \"Our study shows people who spend more time on Facebook spend less time studying,\" said Aryn Karpinski, a researcher. \"Every generation has its distractions , but I think Facebook is a unique phenomenon.\" Karpinski and a colleague questioned 219 US undergraduates and graduates about their study and general Internet use, as well as their specific use of Facebook. They found 65% of Facebook users accessed the...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage ?", "options": ["Facebook fans do worse in exams", "Social networking sites and their fans", "Facebook helps organize social activities", "How to use social networking sites correctly."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3427, "question": "I was at a busy traffic crossing waiting to cross to the other side. There was a family--a man, his wife and an old lady, waiting to cross with me. Then, the light turned green and all of us walked quickly across the road. The light lasted very short, and changed into red in no time. I noticed that both the man and his wife had crossed along with me and the old lady was left behind. I quickly realized what happened. When the light turned dreen again, I ran over to the other side, offered the old lady my right hand and we quickly walked together to the other side of the road. I used my left hand to stop any oncoming traffic so that even if the crossing signal turned red, we cuold make it to the other side safely. In the meantime, both the man and his wife realized that they had left the old...\n\nQ: Why didn't the old lady cross the road with the others ?", "options": ["She wanted them to go first.", "She was too old to walk quickly.", "She didn't see the light changed.", "She wanted them to walk with her."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2530, "question": "Scientists are using a kind of eye-tracking equipment to learn how babies look at the world. In the lab, children 5 months and older crawl and walk up, down and over adjustable wooden slopes , gaps and steps. It may seem like the set for a new reality television show, but there are no prizes, except perhaps for the researchers. They hope to understand what makes one child respond to another, how babies adjust their look to their hands and feet to handle objects, and how these very young children adapt to changes. The findings provided by these eye-trackers suggest that babies may be more capable of understanding and acting on what they see than had been thought. \"Quick looks at their mothers' faces may be all they need to get the information they want. They seem to be surprisingly efficien...\n\nQ: The text is most probably taken from  _  .", "options": ["a website about relationship between mothers and children", "a science magazine about children's actions", "a book about how to teach children", "a newspaper about processing information"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1700, "question": "When 15-year-old Louisa Ball takes a nap, she sleeps for days on end, and no amount of shaking can fully wake her up. The British girl has a rare condition called Sleeping Beauty Sickness. Doctors don't know what causes it or how to cure it --only know that it strikes teenagers and goes away by itself after eight to 12 years. Louisa's mum, Lottie, told NBC News that the girl had flulike symptoms just over a year ago. Shortly afterward, she had her first period of long sleeping. She was eventually diagnosed with Kleine-Levin Syndrome, whose victims worldwide may number no more than 1,000. The victims live normally for weeks or months at a time, with normal sleep patterns and normal energy levels. Then, with little warning, they'll go to sleep for days or weeks at a time. So far, Louisa's lo...\n\nQ: What can we learn about Louisa?", "options": ["Louisa is fond of dancing.", "Louisa can still manage finish her schoolwork without difficulty.", "Louisa is a British girl who likes sleeping.", "Louisa's longest sleeping period is 8 years."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 491, "question": "WILD WEATHERMAN Name: Sam Champion Hot job: TV Weatherman Where: ABC-TV, New York City When you were a child, did you plan to forecast wind, rain, and snow on TV? I wanted to be a foreign journalist. I took courses in weather science at Eastern Kentucky University, but I majored in broadcasting news. How did you finally become a weatherman? My first job in the early 1980s was at the local TV station in Paducah, Kentucky. I did everything from turning on the lights in the morning to writing and delivering morning news. I put together weather forecasts, and became interested in them. Back then, how did you forecast weather? Independent companies collected computer information that showed, for example, how a single weather system might split into snow or snow mixed with rain. The information ...\n\nQ: Present weather forecasting technology   _   .", "options": ["has made weather report more exact than ever", "is still not perfect", "hasn't changed much in the last 50 years", "both A and B"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2609, "question": "More than two thirds of the world's polar bears will be wiped out by 2050,according to a shocking new study. By then,scientists say,global warming will have melted 42 percent of the Arctic sea ice. By 2100,only a very few of these important creatures will be left. The report has been produced by the US Geological Survey. The scientists have publicized their findings in the hope of influencing US Interior Secretary Dirk Kempthorne,who has been asked to put polar bears on the US endangered species list. Polar bears depend on floating sea ice as a platform for hunting seals,which are their main food. Without enough ice,polar bears would be forced to go onto the land,where they are poorly skilled hunters,and would be unlikely to adapt to the life on the land in time. Experts say few little bea...\n\nQ: After a six-month study,some scientists fear that   _  .", "options": ["there is something wrong with their computers", "polar bears will disappear even faster than they ever expected", "their computer models are not as accurate as they expected", "global warming will destroy everything in the Arctic"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2440, "question": "It is a reply to a letter written by Zhai Mingjun, a 16-year-old girl in the class. The two astronauts thank the student for her concerns and wish the class luck in their future studies. \"I' m so happy that the two space men replied with a few encouraging words,\" said Zhai. Her letter was one of the 10 winning letters taken into space by Fei and Nie, who have succeeded in traveling space in the Sixth Shenzhou Spaceship. Zhai wrote the letter as if she were a younger sister of the astronauts. \"As the single child in my family, I always hoped that I would have an elder brother that I could be proud of,\" Zhai said. \"I thought that the astronauts would be lonely during such a long space trip. I hoped they would feel happy and warm when reading my letter.\" Many of Zhai' s classmates also wrote ...\n\nQ: \"Such a great scientific achievement\" refers to  _  .", "options": ["China' s future space program", "The achievement that US astronauts achieved", "Fei and Nie succeeded in traveling space in the Sixth Shenzhou Spaceship.", "Fei and Nie made their head upside down in the spaceship"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3020, "question": "For years we have been dieting strictly after the year-end overeating, afraid that when summer. comes, the bigger size we have accumulated will betray how we ate. Now scientists say, it's a little bug that causes obesity . As the holiday season with its abundant feasting arrives, millions of food lovers are keeping an eye on their figures. But scientists have found that weight gain is not about too much Christmas turkey or hot chocolates, but some bacteria in your guts . Chinese scientists recently discovered a type ofbacteria in guts that may be to blame for obesity. A research team led by Zhao Liping, a professor in Shanghai, has identified a precise link between a particular kind ofbacteria and unusual weight gain. \"The endotoxin released by the bacterium can activate a gene that helps ...\n\nQ: We diet strictly after the year-end overeating because  _  .", "options": ["we won't betray ourselves", "we eat too much turkey", "there are bacteria in our guts", "we don't want to look fat"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2328, "question": "Teenagers are under a lot of pressure to be thin. They resort to starving, vomiting and eating only diet foods to try and be thin. Television is a big influence on them. They watch shows like Beverly Hills 90210 andMelrose Placeand feel they need to look as thin as the actresses on these shows. Society is brainwashing young people into believing that being thin is important and necessary. Diet commercials are constantly appearing on our television screens telling us that once we lose weight, we will be happy. While you're standing at the grocery store you are surrounded by magazines claiming to have the newest and best diet. Each month another new diet appears claiming to be the diet to end all diets. If diets really worked, then why are there so many of them? The reason a new diet pops up...\n\nQ: What areBeverly Hills 90210andMeltrose Place ?", "options": ["Fashion shows.", "Two famous place in America.", "Popular TV shows.", "Two TV channels."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 223, "question": "Bob was born in Cambridge. When he was in elementary school, he asked his mother to take him to parks in their community so he could collect empty soda cans to recycle. His mother agreed, as long as he saved part of the money he earned for college. Bob's mother remembers Bob as the most determined of her seven kids. Bob's persistence paid off. On Friday, he will become the first person in his family, originally from El Salvador, to graduate from college. And he's graduating with university honors. For his honors thesis he researched unmanned solar-powered airplanes, which BYU students have been building and testing for about 10 years. Bob's study helps discover the best way to fly a solar-powered airplane so that it uses the least amount of power. The goal is to design and build an airplan...\n\nQ: People thought Bob couldn't graduate from college because  _  .", "options": ["his parents had little money to support him", "his teacher didn't think he could graduate", "he didn't work hard on his study", "he didn't dare to face the obstacles for short of confidence"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2726, "question": "Two people have died after two separate university shootings in Texas and Arizona, just hours apart. One person was killed and three injured in the first shooting at Northern Arizona University early on Friday. Later that morning a shooting at a student complex near Texas Southern University left one person dead. In Arizona, police named the gunman there as Steven Jones, an 18-year-old first year student at Northern Arizona University.Mr. Jones told police he was approached by a group of men and attacked. He fled, produced a gun from his pocket and opened fire when the men caught up with him, Arizona police said. Witnesses told police that the victims were unarmed. The second shooting in Texas happened later on Friday morning at the University Courtyard Apartments on the edge of the Housto...\n\nQ: Which of the following is right about the Northern Arizona University shooting?", "options": ["The gunman was about to graduate.", "It was the victims who started the fight.", "The gunman shot the victims out of hatrd.", "The victims attacked the gunman with knives."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1726, "question": "When we see well, we do not think about our eyes very often. It is only when we cannot see perfectly that we realize how important our eyes are. People who are near-sighted can only see things that are very close to their eyes. Everything else seems blurry (unclear). Many people who do a lot of work, such as writing, reading and sewing become near--sighted. People who are far-sighted _ from just the opposite problem. They can see things that are far away, but they have difficulty in reading a book unless they hold it at arm's length. If they want to do much reading, they must get glasses, too. Other people do not see clearly because their eyes are not exactly the right shape. They have what is called astigmatism . This, too, can be corrected by glasses. Some people's eyes become cloudy bec...\n\nQ: We should take good care of our eyes  _  .", "options": ["only when we can see well", "only when we cannot see perfectly", "even if we can see well", "only when we realize how important our eyes are"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 76, "question": "Some people collect stamps. Other people collect works of art or musical instruments. But a man in the American state of Maryland collects secrets. For the past 10 years, people have been sending Frank Warren postcards and other objects with secrets written on them. He now has a million secrets. \"It's a drawing of a lift. And the secret says: 'I feel guilty when I take lifts for one floor, so I limp when I get out.'\" Frank said. Ten years ago, Mr. Warren created an art project called PostSecret. People then began to send him postcards, other objects and emails telling their secrets. Every Sunday, he chooses 10 secrets and puts them on the website. Mr. Warren says he created PostSecret so people could share their secrets in a safe place. \"I was struggling with secrets in my own life. And it...\n\nQ: What was Mr. Warren's secret according to the passage?", "options": ["He once took the lift only for one floor.", "He is interested in collecting others' secrets.", "He created an art project without telling his wife.", "He helped prevent others from committing suicides."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 161, "question": "There is no doubt about it.The best way to learn new words is to do it unconsciously.I don't mean while you're unconscious.I mean while you are unconscious of the fact that it is sinking in. That is how I learnt the 30,000 words in my vocabulary by living in an English-speaking world, mother tongue.I just pick them up.But some of _ may be misunderstood.Now, to misunderstand does not mean not to understand.To misunderstand is to understand but incorrectly. The 5 % mislearnt of all the words we \"know\" will be the least frequently used words, as the more frequently used words are less likely to be mislearnt.Some of the misunderstandings may live with all our lives, without knowing that we got them wrong. Many English teachers think that this natural method of learning words in one's own mothe...\n\nQ: It is certain that the best way to learn new words is   _  .", "options": ["to learn them by oneself", "to learn by living in an English-speaking world and using them frequently", "to guess them from the context", "to get more separate meanings of each word"], "answer": 3}]